Inventory of the Citizens for Reagan Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Audio-video campaign materials, 1975-1976 (Folder On shelf)
  - Compact sound cassettes (phonotapes), 1970-1980, undated. (Box 112-120)
    - 1976 Campaign audio recordings (Tape 112-119)
      - Alhumbra, May 28 (Tape 118: 3)
      - Long Beach/Pasa Robeles, May 28-29 (Tape 118: 4)
      - Pasa Robeles; in-flight interviews, May 29 (Tape 118: 5)
      - Bakersfield lunch, June 1 (Tape 118: 6)
      - Fresno, June 1 (Tape 118: 7)
      - Fresno dinner; Stockton, June 1-2 (Tape 118: 8)
      - SACTO; Rhodesia, June 2 (Tape 118: 9)
      - Palo Alto, June 2 (Tape 118: 10)
      - San Francisco press conference, June 3 (Tape 118: 11)
      - RR, June 3 (Tape 118: 12)
      - SB; Lou Cannon, June 3 (Tape 118: 13)
      - LA; Columbus, June 4-5 (Tape 118: 14)
      - Cleveland, June 5 (Tape 118: 15)
      - Cleveland, June 5-6 (Tape 118: 16)
      - Dayton/Cincinnati, Ohio, June 6 (Tape 118: 17)
        Use copy reference number: 81141_a_0011958.
      - master copy: June 6-7 (Tape 118: 18)
      - June 7 (Tape 118: 19)
      - Voting, June 7-8 (Tape 118: 20)
      - Election night; Missouri, June 8, 11 (Tape 118: 21)
      - Iowa, June 17-18 (Tape 118: 22)
      - Iowa, June 18 (Tape 118: 23)
      - master copy: Iowa delegations; Washington, June 19 (Tape 118: 24)
      - Iowa delegations; Washington, June 19 (Tape 118: 25-26)
      - Jackson, Mississippi, June 24 (Tape 118: 27)
      - Master copy: Mississippi; New York Times interview; Minnesota, June 24-25 (Tape 118: 28)
      - Mississippi; New York Times interview; Minnesota, June 24-25 (Tape 118: 29)
      - Minnesota, June 25 (Tape 118: 30-31)
      - Montana; Idaho; California, June 26 (Tape 118: 32)
      - Ronald Reagan taping, June 5 (Tape 118: 33)
      - North Dakota; Colorado, July 7-9 (Tape 118: 34)
      - Colorado, July 9 (Tape 118: 35)
      - New Jersey, July 14-16 (Tape 118: 36)
      - Hotel Utah; State Convention; Airplane; Kansas City; L. Cannon, July 16-17 (Tape 118: 37)
      - Ronald Reagan Today Show; Bergholst; CBS Terry Drinkwater, July 20-24 (Tape 118: 38)
      - ABC History Interview; CBS Jerry, July 24 (Tape 119: 1)
      - Mississippi delegates/press conference, August 4 (Tape 119: 2)
      - Mississippi; ABC; NBC; on-plane interviews; New York Times; Newsweek; New Jersey Landing, August 4-5 (Tape 119: 3)
      - Brooklyn, New Jersey; Philly press conference, August 5-6 (Tape 119: 4)
      - master copy: West Virginia, August 7, 13 (Tape 119: 5)
      - West Virginia, August 7, 13 (Tape 119: 6)
      - CBS Interviews, August 11 (Tape 119: 7)
      - Sears, August 13 (Tape 119: 8)
      - Kansas City, August 15 (Tape 119: 9)
      - Sears for Reagan People, August 15 (Tape 119: 10)
      - Kansas City; Indiana; Alaska, August 16 (Tape 119: 11)
      - Black Caucus; Virginia; Youth Rally, August 16 (Tape 119: 12)
      - Illinois; Louisiana; Oklahoma, August 17 (Tape 119: 13)
      - Mississippi; Iowa; Guam, August 17 (Tape 119: 14)
      - Kansas; Minnesota, August 17-18 (Tape 119: 15)
      - Interview; farewell to staff; August 19 (Tape 119: 16)
      - master copy: August 19-20 (Tape 119: 17)
      - Interviews, August 19-20 (Tape 119: 18)
      - Interviews continued, August 20 (Tape 119: 19)
      - GOP Convention August 1976 (Tape 119: 20-21)
    - Miscellaneous audio recordings, undated, 1970-1980 (Tape 119)
      - Storage tape, undated (Tape 119: 22)
      - Cued to Just After Re Campaign Funds, undated (Tape 119: 23)
      - Unidentified, undated (Tape 119: 24)
      - Reagan Radio Spots, Texas, undated (Tape 119: 25)
      - Tribute to Ronald Reagan, 1974 (Tape 119: 26)
      - Ronald Reagan, Washington D.C., leadership conference, March 8, 1975 (Tape 119: 27)
      - Ronald Reagan, Marshall Town, Iowa, April 25, 1975 (Tape 119: 28)
      - Ronald Reagan Speech and Q and A at Georgia Tech, Atlanta, April 29, 1975 (Tape 119: 29)
      - Face the Nation, June 1, 1975 (Tape 119: 30)
      - Ronald Reagan, Chicago Executive Club, September 26, 1975 (Tape 119: 31)
      - Impromptu news conference, Boca Raton College, FL, November 3, 1975 (Tape 119: 32)
      - Washington, D.C, announcement of candidacy and press conference, November 20, 1975 (Tape 119: 33)
      - Washington, D.C., news conference; Miami rally; Miami news conference, November 20, 1975 (Tape 119: 34)
      - Miami press conference, November 20, 1975 (Tape 119: 35)
      - Manchester, New Hampshire, press conference, November 20, 1975 (Tape 119: 36)
      - Manchester, New Hampshire, Q and A, November 20, 1975 (Tape 119: 36)
      - Charlotte, N.C., press conference, November 21, 1975 (Tape 119: 37)
      - Los Angeles press conference, November 21, 1975 (Tape 120: 1)
      - Charlotte rally; Charlotte news conference; Chicago news conference, November 21, 1975 (Tape 120: 2)
      - Chicago press conference, November 21, 1975 (Tape 120: 3)
      - Governor Reagan's Portrait unveiling, state capitol, November 21, 1975 (Tape 120: 4)
      - Portland, Oregon, GOP Dinner at Eugene Oregon, December 1, 1975/ Lafayette, Louisiana, Chamber of Commerce Dinner December 9, 1975 (Tape 120: 5)
      - Convention, 1976 (Tape 120: 6)
      - Ronald Reagan remarks, Kansas City, Republican convention, undated (Tape 120: 7)
      - Ronald Reagan Bishop Auditorium, May 3, 1977 (Tape 120: 8)
      - Reagan, undated (Tape 120: 9)
      - Galbraith, Democracy and Leadership; Ronald Reagan, An Alternative View, undated (Tape 120: 10)
      - AFRTS-SCN Radio, February 8, 1978 (Tape 120: 11)
      - NACM 82nd Annual Credit Congress, #6 Luncheon Address, the Honorable Ronald Reagan May 21-25, 1978 (Tape 120: 12)
      - October 2, 1978 (Tape 120: 13)
      - Tribute to Theodore Cummings, February 4, 1979 (Tape 120: 14)
      - Announcement of Candidacy, November 13, 1979 (Tape 120: 15)
      - South Carolina Debate: Ronald Reagan, Bush, Baker, Connally, February 28, 1980 (Tape 120: 16)
      - Texas Debate: Reagan vs. Bush, April 24, 1980 (Tape 120: 17)
      - Tape of suggestions for Reagan from elderly supporter, undated (Tape 120: 18)
      - Johnson/MacNamara Administration, Falsifying The News, late 1967 (Tape 120: 19)
      - Johnson/Clifford Administration, Overwhelming Military Superiority, late 1968 (Tape 120: 19)
      - Nixon/Laird Administration, TS Soviet War Plans in Pentagon, early 1970 (Tape 120: 19)
      - Reagan Spots, 1960s (Tape 120: 20)
      - How to Defend America, M. Stanton Evans and Admiral Chester Ward: Two interviews, late 1967, late 1971 (Tape 120: 21)
      - Phyllis Schlafly, Disarming Henry Kissinger, 1975 (Tape 120: 22)
      - Professor Friedman, undated (Tape 120: 23)